=Romance of a Twin Flower=
= رومانسية زهرة مزدوجة =
=Episode 10=
= الحلقة 10 =
Okay, see you tomorrow.
حسنًا، أراك غدًا
Your Lordship.
سيادتك
I led some men
قاد بعض الرجال
to patrol again.
للدورية مرة أخرى
Some people looked suspicious.
بدا بعض الناس مشبوها
Is everything set up?
هل كل شيء مُرتب؟
Yes.
نعم
Why are you looking at me?
لماذا تنظر إليّ؟
Tonight,
الليلة
you'll sleep in the woodshed with me.
ستنامين في الحرير معي
Why
لماذا
would I do that?
هل أفعل ذلك؟
Gui Bai.
جي باي
Yes.
نعم
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I have many enemies.
لدي الكثير من الأعداء
It won't be a safe journey.
لن تكون رحلة آمنة
For those assassins,
لأولئك القاتل
this premium room…
غرفة الأقساط هذه...
Will be
ستكون
their first target.
هدفهم الأول
No wonder
لا عجب
you didn't fight me for the room.
أنت لم تتشاجرني إلى الغرفة
You're using me as a target.
أنت تستغلني كهدف
Right?
صحيح
Let's go.
لنذهب
It's not safe here.
المكان ليس آمنًا هنا
What about Muxu?
ماذا عن موكس؟
Your Ladyship, don't worry.
سيادتك، لا تقلق
I'll take care of her.
سأهتم بها
Can I not go to the woodshed?
ألا يمكنني الذهاب إلى الحطب؟
No.
لا
- I won't sleep in the same bed... - Shush.
- لن أنام في السرير نفسه... - - آسفة
with you.
معك
What are you looking at?
إلام تنظر؟
I can see nothing.
لا شيء
Don't make any trouble.
لا تتسبب في أي مشكلة
Stop playing tricks.
كفّ عن الحيل
I didn't see any other customers
لم أر أي زبائن آخرين
in this inn.
في هذا النزل
How could there be an assassin?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك قاتل؟
You must be unwilling
يجب أن تكون غير راغبة
to let me sleep in the premium room.
أن أنام في غرفة الأقساط
So, you're doing this on purpose, right?
إذًا أنت تفعل هذا عمدًا، صحيح؟
If you think this way,
إذا فكرت بهذه الطريقة
then so be it.
فليكن ذلك إذن
I'm warning you
أنا أحذرك
that I'm not going to share a bed
أنني لن أتقاسم سريرا
with you.
معك
Do you hear me?
هل تسمعينني؟
What are you looking at?
إلام تنظر؟
(If you are not Nie Sangyu,)
(إذا لم تكن ني سانغيو)
(then who are you?)
(إذن من أنت؟)
(I saw a plum blossom shaped birthmark)
(رأيت علامة مميزة على شكل زهر البرقوق)
(on Nie Sangyu's back shoulder.)
(على كتف ني سانغوي في الظهر)
Why are you staring at me?
لماذا تحدق بي؟
Tell you what,
قل لك ماذا
you must not have any impure thoughts.
لا بد ألا يكون لديك أي أفكار جامدة
You heard that?
هل سمعت ذلك؟
There's only one premium room.
هناك غرفة علاوة واحدة فقط
Move.
افسح الطريق
I've been waiting for you for quite a while.
كنت في انتظارك لفترة طويلة
Wake up.
استيقظ
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Don't touch me.
لا تلمسني
Be quiet.
اصمت
I'll call for help.
سأطلب المساعدة
Let go of me.
اتركني!
Listen.
اسمعي
Calm down.
اهدأ
Assassins?
قاتل؟
Then let's run.
إذن دعنا نركض
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
You just stay here.
تبقى هنا فحسب
I won't let anything happen to you.
لن أسمح لك بأي شيء
Trust me.
ثق بي
Where are you going?
إلى أين ستذهب؟
Be careful.
انتبهوا
Let's go.
لنذهب
Your Lordship,
سيادتك
all assassins were killed.
قتل جميع القاتل
We must not take this lightly.
ويجب ألا نستخف بهذا
Ling Jianxing
لينغ جيانشينغ
won't just send these assassins.
لن يرسل فقط هؤلاء القاتل
Send two men to protect my wife.
أرسل رجلين لحماية زوجتي
Yes, Your Lordship.
نعم، سيادتك
All the others,
جميع الآخرين
take your weapons and follow me out
خذوا أسلحتكم واتبعوني
to give them a surprise.
لإعطائهم مفاجأة
(Under professional movement instructions, no animal was harmed)
(بموجب تعليمات الحركة المهنية لم يتعرض أي حيوان للأذى
Where is Ning Yuxuan?
أين نينغ يويشوان؟
Your Ladyship,
سيادتك
His Lordship told us
قال لنا سيادته
to protect you here.
لحمايتك هنا
I'm going to find him.
سأجده
Go.
اذهب
Ning Yuxuan!
نينغ يوتشيوان!
Your Ladyship.
سيادتك
Don't move.
لا تتحركي
One more move,
حركة أخرى
and I'll kill her.
و سأقتلها
I worried about you.
أنا قلق عليك
So, I ran out.
لذلك، نفذت
Tell your men
أخبري رجالك
to back off five miles away.
على بعد خمسة أميال
Right now.
الآن
Sir,
سيدي
it's no use
لا فائدة من ذلك
to threaten him with me.
لتهديده معي
You're wasting your time.
أنت تضيعين وقتك
It's my fault this time.
إنه خطئي هذه المرة
I'll take it on myself.
سآخذه على نفسي
You may leave.
يمكنك المغادرة
Back off.
تراجع
Your Lordship...
سيادتك...
Back off!
تراجع!
Ning Yuxuan,
نينغ يوتشيوان
put your sword down.
ضع سيف خاص بك
Go.
اذهب
Father.
أيها الأب
Yuxuan.
يوتشوان
Put your sword down.
ضع سيف الخاص بك
Father, no, Father!
يا أبي، لا يا أبي!
Father.
أبي
Put your sword down!
ضع سيفك!
Father!
أبي!
Yuxuan,
يوي شوان
close your eyes.
أغمضي عينيك
Put your sword down.
ضع سيفك منخفضا
Father, no, Father!
لا يا أبي!
No.
لا
No, Father.
لا يا أبي
Father!
أبي!
Walk over.
امشي
Leave me alone. Just go.
دعني وشأني، اذهب فحسب
Ning Yuxuan,
نينغ يوتشوان
just go, and leave me alone.
اذهب فحسب، وانفرد بي
Sir,
سيدي
let's just talk.
دعنا نتحدث فحسب
You have my life.
لديك حياتي
You can kill me.
يمكنك أن تقتلني
Don't hurt him.
لا تؤذيه
No.
لا
Ning Yuxuan!
نينغ يوتشيوان!
Ning Yuxuan.
نينغ يوتشوان
How do you feel?
كيف تشعرين؟
Jump.
قفز
(Yifang Inn)
(مسكن ييفانغ)
Your Lordship, you're awake.
سيادتك، أنت مستيقظة
Did you catch them all?
هل أمسكت بهم جميعا؟
We killed half of them
قتلنا نصفهم
and caught the rest.
وأقبض على الباقي
But those caught killed themselves
لكن الذين تم القبض عليهم قتلوا أنفسهم
before we could interrogate them.
قبل أن نتمكن من استجوابهم
It's okay.
لا بأس
I know
أعرف
who is behind this.
من يقف وراء هذا
We're close to Haifang.
نحن قريبون من هيفانغ
Mr. Ling has become more anxious.
أصبح السيد لينغ أكثر قلقا
They don't want me to get near Haifang.
إنهم لا يريدوني أن أقترب من هايفانغ
I'm not that easy to be dealt with.
أنا ليس من السهل التعامل معي
Your Lordship,
سيادتك
you're foresighted and blessed.
أنت متعب ومبارك
Nothing bad would happen to you.
لا شيء سيء سيحدث لك
But Your Lordship,
ولكن سيادتك
why did you put your sword down?
لماذا وضعت سيفك؟
Your Lordship, you passed out last night.
سيادتك، لقد فقدت الوعي الليلة الماضية
It's Her Ladyship who brought you back.
إنها سيدتها هي من أعدك
Where is Nie Sangyu?
أين نيه سانغيوي؟
She's decocting the herbs in the yard
إنها تفسخ الأعشاب في الفناء
for treating your wound.
لعلاج جرحك
Send someone back to the capital immediately
أرسل شخصا ما إلى العاصمة على الفور
to find out Nie Sangyu's whereabouts.
لمعرفة مكان وجود نيه سانغيو
Isn't she in the yard?
أليست في الفناء؟
She
هي
may not be Nie Sangyu.
قد لا تكون نيه سانغيو
Nie Sangyu has a birthmark on her shoulder,
لديه هوية ميلاد على كتفها
but I didn't see it on her.
لكنني لم أرها
Then who is the one in the yard?
إذًا من هو الذي في الفناء؟
Go find it out.
اذهب واكتشف ذلك
Yes, Your Lordship.
نعم، سيادتك
I am the hostess of this mansion.
أنا مضيفة هذا القصر
I don't allow you to marry her.
أنا لا أسمح لك بالزواج منها
Since we can't be a couple
نظرا لأننا لا نستطيع أن نكون زوجين
in this life,
في هذه الحياة
no one else can think about it.
لا يمكن لأحد أن يفكر في الأمر
Honey.
عزيزي
I heard
سمعت
there was some misunderstanding
كان هناك سوء فهم ما
between us.
بيننا
But I believe that
لكنني أعتقد أنه
it won't affect
لن يؤثر
our relationship, right?
على علاقتنا، صحيح؟
Nie Sangyu.
نيه سانغيوي
Your crime of disturbing
جريمة القلق الخاصة بك
the Ning's Mansion is unforgivable.
طائفة نينغ لا تغتفر
Why should I admit to
لماذا يجب أن أعترف
something I haven't done?
شيء لم أفعل؟
Nie Sangyu has studied lower script since she was a child,
درس نيه سانغيو كتابةً أقل منذ أنها كانت طفلة
and her characters are delicate.
وشخصياتها دقيقة
But these profound and powerful words
لكن هذه الكلمات العميقة والقوية
cannot be written
لا يمكن كتابتها
without more than ten years of practice.
دون أكثر من عشر سنوات من الممارسة
Ever since I fell off a cliff,
منذ أن وقعت في هضبة
I've lost all my memories
لقد فقدت كل ذكرياتي
before the fall.
قبل الخريف
I survived by luck.
نجوت محظوظا
So,
لذلك
it's kind of a rebirth.
هذا نوع من الجديد
So did something else
إذًا هل حدث شيء آخر
pop out
مبيد آفات شديد الخطورة
of your mind?
من عقلك؟
Something else?
شيء آخر؟
For example,
على سبيل المثال
memories from the past.
ذكريات من الماضي
♪Once anchored in your rainy eyes♪
♪ بمجرد أن ترسخ في عينيك الماطرين ♪
(Your Ladyship, you're finally back.)
(سيدتك، لقد عدت أخيرا)
I was so scared.
كنت خائفا جدا
How did His Lordship
كيف قام الملك
get injured so badly?
أصيب بجروح بالغة؟
Your Ladyship, are you all right?
سيادتك، هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير
Muxu,
موكس
did you prepare these herbs
هل قمت بإعداد هذه الأعشاب
by following the prescription?
عن طريق اتباع الوصفة الطبية؟
There must be no mistake.
يجب ألا يكون هناك أي خطأ
They were all prepared
كانوا جميعا مستعدين
according to your instructions.
وفقا لتعليماتكم
That's good.
هذا جيد
(I should have guessed it.)
"كان يجب أن أحافظ على ذلك"
(You couldn't be)
(لا يمكن أن تكون)
(the same person.)
(الشخص نفسه)
Your Ladyship,
سيادتك
have you noticed
هل لاحظت
that His Lordship's attitude towards you
أن موقف سيادته تجاهك
has changed a lot recently?
قد تغير كثيرا مؤخرا؟
He seems
يبدو
not as indifferent as before.
ليس غير مبال كما كان من قبل
This time, he even…
هذه المرة، حتى...
Ning Yuxuan,
نينغ يوتشوان
put your sword down.
ضع سيف خاص بك
♪Looking at the rippling waves in the starry river♪
♪ النظر في موجات النهضة في نهر الجوت ♪
♪And plucking at the strings in my heart♪
♪ والعلق على خيط في قلبي ♪
♪Who has noticed their feelings for each other♪
♪ من لاحظ مشاعرهما لبعضهم البعض ♪
Your Ladyship?
سيادتك؟
Your Ladyship.
سيادتك
Indeed,
بالفعل
he has changed a lot.
لقد تغير كثيرا
He has become so lecherous.
لقد أصبح رائعا جدا
(He always tries to harass me.)
(إنه يحاول دائما مضايقتي)
(But)
(لكن)
(who are you?)
(من أنت؟)
(Why do you)
(لماذا أنت)
(look exactly the same as her?)
(تبدو مثلها تماما؟)
(Why did you)
(لماذا ظهرت أمامي فجأة)
(suddenly appear in front of me?)
(ظهرت أمامي فجأة؟)
Boss.
أيها الزعيم
What have you found?
ماذا وجدت؟
Only guards from the Marquis's Mansion.
فقط الحراس من مقصورة ماركيز
There's no sign of Ning Yuxuan
لا توجد علامة على نينغ يويشوان
and Ms. Nie.
والسيدة ني
Well,
إذن
Ning Yuxuan is really lucky.
ننغ يويشوان محظوظ حقا
He escaped once again.
هرب مرة أخرى
Boss,
أيها الزعيم
who do you think
من في رأيك
are trying to kill Ning Yuxuan?
يحاول قتل نينغ يويشوان؟
Are they from the Tea Gang too?
هل هم من تاي غانغ أيضا؟
It must be Ning Yuxuan's opponent.
لا بد أنه خصم نينغ يوتشيوان
(It's too risky to be around Ning Yuxuan.)
(من الخطورة بمكان أن يكون حول نينغ يوتشوان)
(I must get my little sister away from him)
(يجب أن أبعد أختي الصغيرة عنه)
(as soon as possible.)
(في أقرب وقت ممكن)
Boss.
رئيسا
Why are you looking at me like that?
لماذا تنظرين إليّ هكذا؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك
No thanks.
لا شكراً
I'm the one who should say thanks.
أنا من يجب أن شكر
If it wasn't for me,
لولا أجلي
you wouldn't get injured so badly.
ما كنت لتتأذي بشدة
It has nothing to do with you.
لا شيء يخصك
Why do you say that?
لماذا تقول ذلك؟
Didn't you put your sword down
ألم تضع سيفك
for protecting me?
لحمايتي؟
Is it hurting again?
هل يؤلمك مرة أخرى؟
I'm okay.
أنا بخير
Can you promise me
هل يمكنك أن تعديني
not to drop your sword again
عدم إسقاط سيفك مرة أخرى
if that happens again?
إذا حدث ذلك مرة أخرى؟
No matter who it is for, including me.
لا يهم من يكون، بما في ذلك أنا
Do you hear me?
هل تسمعوني؟
Yes.
نعم
Including me.
بما في ذلك أنا
Sit by my side.
اجلس بجانبي
Sit by my side. Can't you hear me?
اجلس بجانبي، ألا تسمعينني؟
Come on.
هيا
Be careful.
كن حذرا
♪Young man admires the flowers and smiles♪
♪ شاب معجب الأزهار والبساتين ♪
♪Birds swaying on the branches♪
♪ الطيور تتبدل على الفروع ♪
♪The warm wind chasing after the shadow♪
♪ الرياح الدافئة تطارد بعد الظل ♪
No need.
لا حاجة
♪I'm happy to see your smiling face♪
♪ أنا سعيدة لرؤية وجهك المبتسم ♪
Come on.
هيا
No.
لا
Don't move.
لا تتحركي
Or your wound will hurt again.
أو سيجرح جرحك مجددًا
You may
أنت
just lean on me like this.
عليّ بهذه الطريقة فحسب
Do you feel more comfortable?
هل تشعرين بمزيد من الارتياح؟
♪No matter how far the water flows♪
لا يهم إلى أي مدى تتدفق المياه ♪
Just like this.
مثل هذا تماما
You may have a rest.
خذوا قسطا من الراحة
Don't move.
لا تتحركوا
I'm here.
أنا هنا
You may rest assured
أتمنى أن تطمئن
that no one
أن لا أحد
could touch you again.
يمكن أن يلمسك مرة أخرى
Don't let me
لا تدعني
see those people again.
انظر هؤلاء الناس مرة أخرى
Otherwise, I would tear them apart.
خلاف ذلك، سأمزقهم
It's okay. I'm here.
لا بأس أنا هنا
♪No matter how far the water flows♪
♪ بغض النظر عن مدى تدفق المياه ♪
♪And how far the road is♪
♪ وإلى أي مدى الطريق ♪
♪The time and I are growing old with you♪
♪ الوقت وأنا أتقدم في السن معك ♪
♪Let the wind blow♪
♪ دع الرياح تنفد ♪
♪The boat floats in the water♪
♪ يعمر القارب في المياه ♪
Don't move.
لا تتحركوا
♪Smiling while watching shining stars and the bright moon♪
♪ الابتسام بينما تشاهد و ♪ النجوم المشرقة
(In this world,)
(في هذا العالم)
(you're the only one)
(أنت الوحيد)
(who is willing to die with me.)
(الذي على استعداد للموت معي)
(The only thing I can do right now)
(الشيء الوحيد الذي يمكنني فعله الآن)
(is to help you get your memories back)
(هو مساعدتك على استعادة ذكرياتك)
(and solve all mysteries.)
(لحل جميع الأسرار)
(Haifang)
(هيفانغ)
Bravo, bravo!
أحسنتم!
The street is so bustling.
الشارع صاخب جدًا
The magistrate's residence must be more luxurious.
مقر إقامة القاضي لا بد أن يكون أكثر فخمة
Do you enjoy watching this?
هل تستمتعين بمشاهدة هذا؟
Then enjoy yourself.
إذًا استمتع بنفسك
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني؟
We can bet with one bead.
يمكننا المراهنة على حزم واحدة
On what?
على ماذا؟
You would miss the Ning's Mansion
سوف تفتقدين قصر نينغ
after seeing the magistrate's residence.
بعد رؤية مقر إقامة القاضي
Is there any place
هل هناك مكان
even less pleasant than your mansion?
حتى أقل لطفًا من قصتك؟
I can bet with all my beads.
يمكنني المراهنة على كل حبيبتي
You like beads so much.
تحبين الحبال كثيرًا
Then
إذن
I'll call you Hongzhu from now on.
سأتصل بك هونغتشو من الآن فصاعدًا
Hongzhu?
هونغتشو؟
Hongzhu
هونغتشو
sounds like "red pig".
يبدو وكأنه "الخنزير الأحمر"
What kind of name is that?
ما هذا الاسم؟
Then I'll call you Lanzhu.
إذن سأتصل بك لانزو
Lanzhu.
لانزو هو
Lanzhu?
لانزو؟
Yes.
نعم
Lanzhu means
لانزو تعني
lazy pig.
خنزير كسول
Yeah, Lanzhu?
نعم، لانتشو؟
Okay.
نعم ، لانتشو؟ 0سبتمبر0 حسنا. 0سبتمبر0 هونغ تشو.
Hongzhu.
هونغتشو
Lanzhu.
هونغ تشو. 0سبتمبر0 لانتشو. 0سبتمبر0 هونغ تشو.
Lanzhu, Hongzhu.
لانزو، هونغتشو
Fine.
حسنا
At least they sound like a good match.
على الأقل تبدو مثل مباراة جيدة
(No Peace in the World)
(لا سلام في العالم)
Sir.
سيدي
You must have failed again in the mission.
لا بد أنك فشلت في المهمة مرة أخرى
I'm useless.
أنا عديم الفائدة
You can't even do such a little thing.
لا يمكنك حتى فعل مثل هذا الشيء
How should I explain to His Highness?
كيف يجب أن أشرح لسموه؟
Sir,
سيدي
Lord Tan sent someone here
أرسل اللورد تان شخصا إلى هنا
for delivering a secret letter.
لتسليم رسالة سرية
(Don't act rashly.)
(لا تتصرف بسرعة)
(Let Ning enter Haifang.)
(دع نينغ يدخل هيفانغ)
(Work together up and down.)
(اعملوا معا جنبا إلى جنب)
(Borrow a knife to kill him.)
"ألم يقتله سكين"
Good. That's exactly what I want.
جيد، هذا ما أريده تمامًا
In this case,
في هذه الحالة
let's do it in Haifang,
دعنا نفعل ذلك في هيفانغ
catching the rat in the hole.
اللحاق بالفأر في الثقب
Ning Yuxuan.
نينغ يوتشيوان
(Ning)
(نينغ)
(Magistrate's Residence)
(سكن القاضي)
Your Lordship.
سيادتك
It's such a big gift.
إنها هدية كبيرة جدا
Ning Yuxuan,
نينغ يوتشيوان
is this where you'll work
هل هذا هو المكان الذي ستعمل فيه
after traveling so far from the capital?
بعد السفر بعيدا عن العاصمة؟
Yes.
نعم
Well,
إذن
I think
أعتقد أنك
you're not fully recovered yet.
لم تتعافي تماما بعد
Maybe we should go back,
ربما يجب أن نعود
and come back when you're recovered.
وتعودي عندما تتعافى
There is no need.
لا داعي لذلك
After taking your medicine,
بعد تناول الدواء الخاص بك
my wound
جرحي
is almost healed.
قد شُفيت تقريبا
Yeah?
نعم؟
Since we're already here, let's make ourselves at home.
نظرا لأننا هنا بالفعل لنكن في المنزل
Coming here to meet local people by fate.
جئت إلى هنا للقاء السكان المحليين بالمصير
Hoping to...
على أمل...
(Feel less guilty)
(أقل شأنا)
Feel less gullty to the peopie.
لا تشعر بالسوء تجاه الشخص
The words are wrongly written.
الكلمات مكتوبة بشكل خاطئ
Yeah.
نعم
Look,
انظر
even words on the plague are wrongly written.
حتى الكلمات على الطاعون مكتوبة بشكل خاطئ
This is definitely
هذا بالتأكيد
not the right place to work.
ليس هو المكان الصحيح للعمل
Let's go.
لنذهب
There's one stroke missing for "Kui" [*Kui means guilt]
هناك ضربة واحدة مفقودة لـ "الكوي" [* الكوي يعني الذنب]
and one extra stroke for "Min". [*Min means people]
وضربات إضافية واحدة لـ "مين" [* مين يعني الناس]
As a magistrate,
كقاض جزئي
what's wrong
ما هو الخطأ
with hoping to feel less guilty
على أمل أن تشعر بالذنب
and thinking more about the people.
والتفكير أكثر في الناس
How could someone who wrote this couplet
كيف يمكن لشخص كتب هذا الاتفاق
end up
في النهاية
being accused of embezzlement
بتهمة الاختلاس
and jumping off a cliff.
والقفز من الهاوية
Let's go.
لنذهب
Maybe
ربما
there are more surprises inside.
هناك المزيد من المفاجآت في الداخل
Come on.
هيا
Ning Yuxuan.
نينغ يوتشيوان
It's so scary here.
المكان مخيف جدا هنا
Let's not go inside.
دعنا لا ندخل
What's so scary?
ما الأمر مخيف؟
No.
لا
(Law and Conscience)
(القانون والشعور)
Is this the trial hall?
هل هذه هي قاعة المحاكمة؟
It's scarier than a mourning hall.
إنها مخزية من قاعة الحداد
Ning Yuxuan,
نينغ يويشوان
you may stay here
يمكنك البقاء هنا
if you want.
إذا كنت تريد
I won't stay here with you.
لن أبقى هنا معك
I'm not going to stay here alone.
لن أبقى هنا وحدي
It's the rule
هذه هي القاعدة
for the magistrate's family to stay here.
تسمح لعائلة القاضي بالبقاء هنا
If you don't want to stay here,
إذا كنت لا تريدين البقاء هنا
you may go check the backyard.
يمكنك الذهاب إلى الفناء الخلفي
Backyard?
الفناء الخلفي؟
But I must remind you
ولكن يجب أن أذكر لك
that you're a lady with imperial mandate,
أنك سيدة ذات ولاية إمبراطورية
but not a lady calling for help.
لكن ليس سيدة تطلب المساعدة
It's funny.
هذا غريب
How could the backyard
كيف يمكن أن يكون الفناء الخلفي
be like this?
هكذا؟
Yeah, it's so scary.
نعم هذا مخيف جدا
That must be the bedroom.
يجب أن تكون هذه هي غرفة النوم
(Jiangzhen Pavilion)
(جناح جيانغجين)
Come on,
هيا
let's go take a look.
دعنا نذهب ونلق نظرة
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف
It's okay.
لا بأس
(Clean Prudent Diligent)
(دعاية نظيفة)
Your Lordship,
سيادتك
do you want me
هل تريد مني
to find a cook?
العثور على طهي؟
No hurry.
لا تستعجل في هذا
Let's wait for a little while.
لننتظر بعض الوقت
What is this place?
ما هذا المكان؟
Your Ladyship,
سيادتك
I'm afraid to go inside.
أخشى الدخول
What's so scary?
ما هو مخيف؟
I don't believe
لا أعتقد
that there're ghosts
أن هناك أشباح
in broad daylight.
في وضح النهار
Your Ladyship.
سيادتك
My god!
يا إلهي!
Ning Yuxuan.
نينغ يوتشوان
Help!
النجدة!
Help! Ning Yuxuan.
النجدة! نينغ يويشوان
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
In the backyard,
في الفناء الخلفي
there is…
هناك...
What?
ماذا؟
I-It's here.
I-إنه هنا
I was so scared.
كنت خائفًا جدًا
Is this the dead man you told me?
هل هذا هو الرجل الميت الذي أخبرتني به؟
Let go of me.
اتركني!
I'm scared.
أنا خائفة
If you don't let go of me,
إذا لم تتركني
how could I check
كيف يمكنني التحقق
whether there is a dead man inside it?
ما إذا كان هناك رجل ميت في داخلها؟
Why are you talking to me like this?
لماذا تتحدثين إليّ هكذا؟
I'm so scared now.
أنا خائفة جدًا الآن
How can you talk to me
كيف يمكنك التحدث إليّ
like this?
هكذا
Can you be a little more reasonable?
هل يمكنك أن تكون معقولاً أكثر قليلًا
I'm helping you check it.
أنا أساعدك في التحقق من ذلك
I'm a woman.
أنا امرأة
I'm scared.
أنا خائفة
Are you not a woman
ألست امرأة
in normal times?
في الأوقات العادية؟
How can you say that about me?
كيف يمكنك قول ذلك عني؟
It's empty.
لا يوجد شيء
Empty?
فارغ؟
The former magistrate
القاضي السابق
jumped off a cliff with all his families.
قفز من الهاوية مع جميع عائلته
He only left a letter written with blood
ترك رسالة مكتوبة بالدم فقط
to confess his guilt.
للاعتراف بالذنب
None of his families
لا أحد من عائلته
is alive.
على قيد الحياة
Who would set up the mourning hall for him?
من يمكن أن ينشئ قاعة الحداد له؟
And who
ومن
placed the coffin here?
وضع الشيطان هنا؟
So...
لذلك
What?
ماذا؟
This is a warning.
هذا تحذير
I've never provoked them.
لم أستفز منهم أبدا
Why are they warning me?
لماذا يحذرونني؟
They are warning me.
إنهم يحذرون مني
I see.
فهمت
They wanted to
أرادوا أن
scare me.
يخيفني
But these tricks
لكن هذه الحيل
wouldn't scare me off at all.
لن يخيفني على الإطلاق
But they
لكننا
did scare the lady next to me,
أخافوا السيدة بجانبي
a second-rank lady with imperial mandate.
سيدة من الدرجة الثانية ذات ولاية إمبراطورية
Are you kidding?
هل تمزح؟
I just told you
قلت لك للتو
that it was weird inside here.
أنه كان غريبًا في الداخل هنا
It's just as expected.
إنه متوقع فقط
You don't look scared
لا تبدو خائفا
at all.
على الإطلاق
Not at all.
لا على الإطلاق
Since you're not scared,
بما أنك لست خائفا
you'll stay here.
سوف تبقى هنا
You'd better
من الأفضل
get the room cleaned up.
لتنظيف الغرفة
Why is it me to clean it?
لماذا أنا أقوم بتنظيفه؟
Because you said
لأنك قلت
a second-rank lady with imperial mandate
سيدة من الدرجة الثانية ذات ولاية إمبراطورية
has the premium room.
لديها غرفة التعليم
I'm only a county magistrate who can only stay
أنا فقط قاضي مقاطعة يمكن البقاء فقط
in a woodshed or a wing-room.
في مستنقعات أو غرفة نوم
So, I'll go find a wing-room.
لذلك، سأذهب للبحث عن غرفة نوم
No way.
لا يمكن
I disagree.
أنا لا أتفق
You stay in this room and clean it.
أنت تبقى في هذه الغرفة ونظفها
You will have one bead
سيكون لديك حزم واحدة
for cleaning this room.
لتنظيف هذه الغرفة
Would you
هل يمكنك
do it or not?
سواء كان ذلك؟
There's no other choice.
لا داعي لهذا
You're a lazy pig anyway.
أنت خنزير كسول على أي حال
Muxu, get the tools.
موشو، احصل على الأدوات
(Law and Conscience)
(القانون والشعور)
(Clean Prudent Diligent)
(حنكة نظيفة)
Didn't you sleep well last night?
ألم تنم جيدا ليلة أمس؟
You look sleepy.
تبدين نائمةً
Go back to sleep if you feel sleepy.
عد للنوم إن كنت تشعرين بالنعاس
Who...
من
Who cleaned the floor?
من نظّف الأرض؟
Yeah.
نعم
Who cleaned the place?
من نظف المكان؟
Come on.
هيا
Your Lordship.
سيادتك
- Your Lordship.
- سيادتك
I'm the butler here.
أنا الخدم هنا
I didn't know
لم أكن أعرف
that you were coming today.
أنك ستأتي اليوم
Please forgive me
أرجوك سامحني
for not meeting you earlier.
لعدم مقابلتك قبل قليل
It's okay.
لا بأس
The place is already cleaned.
تم تنظيف المكان بالفعل
And it's late today.
وقد تأخر الوقت اليوم
You may go back to rest.
عد إلى الراحة
Tomorrow,
غدًا
do what you should do.
افعل ما عليك فعله
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي
Let's go.
لنذهب
They look so slouchy
يبدون مهتمين جدا
and show little respect for you.
ويبدون احتراما قليلا لك
They act not like servants at all.
إنهم يتصرفون ليسوا كالخدم على الإطلاق
Someone
شخص ما
must have told them to do so.
يجب أن يكون قد طلب منهم القيام بذلك
It seems
يبدو أن شخصا ما
that someone is trying to treat us
أن شخصا ما يحاول أن يعاملنا
the same way
بنفس الطريقة
they treated the former magistrates.
واجهوا القضاة السابقين
Since they want
بما أنهم يريدون
to send me a big gift,
إرسال هدية كبيرة لي
I should think about
يجب أن أفكر
how to return the favor.
كيف تعيد المعروف
♪Summer stars, autumn night♪
♪ النجوم الصيفية، ليلة الخريف ♪
♪Who is wandering under the moon in my heart♪
♪ من يتكاسل القمر في قلبي ♪
♪The deepest story with the shallowest goodbye♪
♪ أعمق قصة الوداع الأكثر ضحالة ♪
♪After passing by, I can only meet you in my dream♪
♪ بعد المرور من هنا لا يمكنني إلا أن ألتقي بك في حلمي ♪
♪The wind can't breeze the long street of time♪
♪ لا يمكن للرياح أن تنمو طريق الوقت الطويل ♪
♪The burning yearning will never cool♪
♪ الشوق المحترق لن يكون رائعا أبدا ♪
♪Two hearts meet again foreshadowing love♪
♪ قلبتان يلتقيان مرة أخرى وينذر بالحب ♪
♪How can I describe it when we look into each other's eyes♪
♪ كيف يمكنني وصفها عندما ننظر في عيون بعضنا البعض ♪
♪Take a life time to write the story♪
♪ خذوا وقت حياة لكتابة القصة ♪
♪Together with you♪
♪ معك ♪
♪Company you♪
♪ الارتباط معك ♪
♪Just for your glance and smile♪
♪ فقط من أجل نظرك وابتسامك ♪
♪The first promise means the forever love♪
♪ الوعد الأول يعني الحب إلى الأبد ♪
♪Fireworks all over the sky light up your night♪
♪ الألعاب النارية في جميع أنحاء السماء ضيء ليلتك ♪
♪Take a life time♪
♪ أخذ وقت الحياة ♪
♪To write the story with you gradually♪
♪ لكتابة القصة معك تدريجيا ♪
♪Just like this♪
♪ هكذا ♪
♪Our love goes on and on♪
♪ حبنا يستمر في النهاية ♪
♪The day we first met, the year when we get old♪
♪ اليوم الذي التقينا فيه لأول مرة السنة عندما نتقدم في السن ♪
♪My heart and my love will never vanish♪
♪ قلبي وحبي لن يختفي أبدًا ♪